Onondaga Community College Publications Collection
Onondaga Community College
Onondaga Community College Publications Collection
1968 - 2018
The Onondaga Community College Publication Collection contains printed materials published by the college from the early years of the college to the present day.
2.5 linear feet
Onondaga Community College
4585 W Seneca Turnpike Syracuse, NY 13215
This collection is open to researchers without restriction.
This collection features publications from the Onondaga Community College. By no means comprehensive, this collection does contain a variety of college publications from the beginnings of the college to the present day. This collection represents many departments and includes a range of formats, from newspapers, newsletters, brochures, and fliers to holiday cards.
newsletters; newspapers; fliers (printed matter); brochures; Christmas cards; Onondaga Community College; College Publications
The Onondaga Community College Publications contains publications from the founding of the college in 1962 to the present day. Publications include newspapers, newsletters, brochures, fliers and card. The topics range from news and information about the college, campus life, student conduct, academic rules, admissions, diversity and campus issues. This collection is updated continuously with the latest issues of the college's publications. Each series is organized into narrower sub-series and then arranged chronologically.
Series 1 - Newsletters - This series contains newsletters covering campus life, academics, administrative activities, and college events created by Onondaga Community College. Date coverage 1968-2018.
Series 2 - Newspapers - Onondaga Community College published several newspapers over the years, covering events and college information. Date coverage 1969-2018.
Series 3 - Brochures - Onondaga Community College has produced numerous brochures, from campus living, student conduct, students rights and responsibilities, visitors guides, and program and event publications. Date coverage 1970-2018.
Series 4 - Cards - Onondaga Community College card collection includes holiday cards from OCC Presidents and the OCC Foundation. Many are designed by faculty and students. Date coverage 1980-2018.
Series 5 - Fliers - Fliers concerning events and college notifications. Date coverage 1980-2000.
- Newsletters, 1968 - 2018
  - "Happenings: a Weekly Calendar of Events and Activities at OCC", 1968 - 1969 (Box-folder PUB7-1)
  - "Out of Touch: Staff News", 1973 - 1975 (Box-folder PUB7-3)
  - "In Touch: A Newsletter Serving the OCC Community", 1970 - 1978 (Box PUB8)
  - "OCCurences: from the Office of the President", 1986 - 1997 (Box-folder PUB9-1)
  - "OCC Bulletin", 1981 (Box-folder PUB9-2,3)
  - "Smoke Signals: Onondaga Chapter", 1968 - 1969 (Box-folder PUB7-3)
  - "It's Academic", 2011 - 2013 (Box-folder PUB7-4)
  - "Admission News", 1981 - 1992 (Box-folder PUB29-7)
  - "Academic Newsletter", 1999 (Box-folder PUB29-7)
  - "Campus Life", 2006 (Box-folder PUB29-7)
  - "Wellness Newsletter", 1988 - 1990 (Box-folder PUB28-2)
  - "Continuum: A Publication of Onondaga Community College and the OCC Foundation and the OCC Alumni Association", June, 2006 - 2012 (Box PUB-38)
- Newspapers, 1969 - 2018
  - "Summer Times", 1969 (Box-folder PUB7-2)
  - "OCC Today", 2002 - 2005 (Box PUB2)
  - "One Hundred Eighty Degrees", 2006 - 2009 (Box PUB2)
  - "Onondaga Global", 2013 - 2014 (Box PUB2)
- Brochures, 1970 - 2018
  - "Academic Rules", 1985 - 2011 (Box-folder PUB29-2)
  - "Student Code of Conduct and Judicial Procedures", 2000 (Box-folder PUB29-1)
  - "Code of Student Rights and Responsibilities", 2001 (Box-folder PUB29-1)
  - "A Guide to Academic Support", 2010 (Box-folder PUB29-3)
  - "Advisory Committee Dinner Publications", 1987 - 1990 (Box-folder PUB29-4)
  - "Campus Cell Phones Tour", 2010 (Box-folder PUB29-5)
  - "OCC Visitor's Guide", 1980-2000 (Box-folder PUB29-6)
  - "College for Living", 1996 (Box-folder PUB29-8)
  - "New Visions for Continued Education: A College Living Program", 2007 (Box-folder PUB29-10)
  - "It's Up to You", 19uu (Box-folder PUB29-11)
  - "Division of Continuing Education - Onondaga Community College", 1970 (Box-folder PUB29-12)
  - Festival of the Arts Publications, 1971 - 1979 (Box-folder PUB5-2)
    - Festival of the Arts Memos, 1969 - 1981 (Box-folder PUB5-1)
  - Advertising and Promotion of the College/General, undated to present (Box PUB30-31)
  - Athletic Yearbooks, undated to present (Box PUB32)
  - Curriculum Brochures, 1964 to present (Box PUB33-34)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, A-Z, undated - present (Box PUB35-37)
    - Includes files: Financial aid; Harassment, Racial and Safety; Christmas Open House; "It's Academic"; International Students Writings; Lincoln Exhibit; Memorial Tributes; Minority Resources; Miscellaneous Art, Music etc. Brochures, undated to present (Box PUB35)
    - Includes files: Academic Computing News; OCC Communique; OCC miscellaneous brochures; OCC Internet Users Manual, undated to present (Box PUB36)
    - Includes files: Scholastic Art; Sports Camps; OCC Staff Development; Ednita Wright article in "Syracuse Woman"; Christina Braunberger publication "Tatoos: Schooled Onondaga Community College; Transfer; Tree Planting Ceremonies; Veterans; "The View from Onondaga"; Workshops and Conferences; Welcome., undated to present (Box PUB37)
  - Recruitment Brochures and Fliers, 2006 - 2018 (Box PUB39)
  - Advertisements - OCC, 2006 - 2018 (Box PUB39)
- Cards, 1980-2018
  - OCC Christmas Cards, 1980's-2000's (Box-folder PUB29-9)
- Fliers, 1980's-2000's
  - Miscellaneous Fliers, 1980's-2000's (Box-folder PUB29-10)